人人影视倾情奉献
翻译   草草
翻译   肉松
翻译   盐湖凉开水
翻译   杏仁斯嘉丽
翻译   苏小黛
翻译   国士章鱼X
翻译   轩辕喵
翻译   Lynn_宁
时间轴   知之
时间轴   壬虚浪影
时间轴   萌
后期   饿得慌
顾问   老杜
校对   草草
总监   草草
纸牌屋
第五季  第四集
全片完
派拉蒙电影
我不懂为什么数据这么低
I don't understand why the numbers are so low.
-根本没道理  -投票率很低
- It doesn't make any sense. - Turnout's bad.
我听说政治新闻网更重关注康威一方
I hear at Politico, they're concentrating mostly on Conway art.
闭嘴  不然就开除你
Shut up or you're fired.
...赛区对手
...division rivals.
这场斗殴很有看点
The fighting was quite a spectacle
但对冰球迷来说  不幸的是
but, unfortunately for hockey fans,
那是昨晚比赛中
that was just about the only action
唯一的看点
to be seen in last night's game.
威尔  马克来了
Will, Mark's here.
希望你睡了会儿
Hope you got some sleep.
其实没有
No, not really.
甚至跑了步  但...
Even went for a run, but...
你饿吗
You hungry?
我只是想在今天
Um, I just wanted to connect
接下来的活动前  告诉你一下
before the rest of this day kicks in.
我跟马歇尔谈过了
I spoke to Marshall.
我告诉他了
No, I told him.
情势很喜人
Things are looking good.
非常喜人
Very good.
我很想感谢你做的一切  那支广告还有...
I really want to thank you for everything. I mean, the ad and--
那支广告和我无关
I had nothing to do with that ad.
当然  但...
No, of course, but...
谢谢你的支持
to thank you for your support.
全靠你自己
This is all you.
听着
Listen...
我...不想说错话
I'm... choosing my words very carefully here.
你得准备好
You need to get ready.
今天会大获全胜
Today's gonna be a good day.
你可以等进白宫再睡
You can sleep when you get to the White House.
但也未必
Or maybe not.
准备好吧  威尔  再见
Get yourself together, Will. I'll see you in a bit.
你准备好
Are you ready...
来"抓"我了吗
to catch me?
道格  莉安  你们有空吗
Doug, LeAnn... do you have a moment?
从山麓酒店现场发来的报道
Reporting live from the Piedmont Hotel,
现场气氛很激烈
the excitement is definitely in the air right now.
最好别让他们看到你证件上的名字
Better not let them see the name on your credentials.
那些人很爱戴他们的总统
Those folks out there love their president.
我很爱磅蛋糕
I love pound cake.
不代表它对我有益
Doesn't mean it's good for me.
你怎么样  赛斯
How are you doing, Seth?
-你这里还有粉底没抹匀  -天啊
- You got some foundation right here. - Oh, jeez.
我们还把这称为新闻
And we call it the news.
我要做实况报道
I'm doing commentary.
那么迟早会有人问我
Which means eventually someone gets to ask me
我的文章有没有影响到总统的败选
if my articles affected the president's loss.
或胜选
Or his win.
祝你顺顺利利  赛斯
I wish you the best, Seth.
你还会找到工作的
You'll land somewhere.
你就是那种人
You're that type.
我们今晚会十分成功
We're going to have a great night tonight.
你没必要哄我
You don't have to spin me.
我应该怎么说
How shall I say this?
我单身时  总是去败选者的派对
When I was single, I always picked the loser's party.
我在鲍勃·多尔的宴会厅认识了
I met the last Mrs. Hammerschmidt drowning in tequila shots
正豪饮龙舌兰的上任太太
at the Bob Dole ballroom.
而我现在...又单身了
And here I am... single again.
-你现在不在德州了  -道格  省省吧
- You're not in Texas anymore. - Doug, please.
-怎么了  -别以为你了解我
- Please what? - Don't think you know me.
我只是想确定你准备好...
Look, I just want to be sure that you're ready for--
麦卡伦会做他该做的事
Macallan will do what he has to.
我喜欢赢
I like to win.
奖杯  奖牌  焦灼的比赛  我都想赢
Trophies, medals, staring contests. You name it.
你能懂这一点  就能懂我
You understand that, you understand me.
大家好
Hello, everyone.
现在为时尚早
Well, it's still early.
今天的大选进程还远远没结束
There's a lot more election to be had today.
我们只是想道个歉
And we just want to apologize that,
因为我们还有点工作要做
because we have a little more work to do,
我们没法早点
we're not gonna be able to get over to the ballroom
抵达宴会厅了
as early as we would like to.
但等我们到了那里
But once we do get there,
我们就会跟你们每一位握手
we are going to shake the hand of each and every one of you,
感谢你们为我们所做的
to thank you for all the extraordinary work
出色工作
that you've done for us.
没错  为大家鼓掌吧
That's right, a round of applause all the way around.
我们等会儿派对上见
And we'll see you all at the party a little later.
好点了吗
Better?
嗯  好了一点
Yeah, a little.
我第一次上了一位总统
First time I've fucked a president.
-不要这样讲  -马歇尔说...
- Oh, don't say that. - Marshall said...
我还不是总统
I'm not a president yet.
就快了
Almost.
我得穿好衣服
I got to put on a suit.
-大家就要来了  -威尔
- People will be here soon. - Will...
你就不能允许自己感受一下吗
can't you let yourself feel it?
就快了
Almost.
-您准备好就开始  先生  -请接通州长
- Ready when you are, sir. - Put the governor on, please.
-你好  -米切  我是总统
- Hello. - Mitch, this is the president.
我知道你听过简报了
I understand you've been briefed.
总统先生
Oh, Mr. President...
这让我们猝不及防
this is catching us all off guard over here.
州的  当地的  我们都不知道
State, local, we had no idea.
我理解
I understand.
我跟副总统  和国务卿杜兰特在一起
I'm with the vice president, the Secretary of State Durant,
反恐处助理局长格林也在线上
and on the line with us is Counterterrorism Director Green.
州长  很抱歉  但我们必须行动
Governor, sir, I'm sorry, but we needed to act.
我直接联系了当地执法部门
I contacted local law enforcement directly.
我是过了好一会儿才知道
Well, it took a while to get to me.
米切  反恐处助理局长要与我们分享一些
Mitch, the Counterterrorism Director will be sharing information
绝不能外泄的信息
that we must keep amongst ourselves.
我们不想做任何会影响今天投票的事
We do not want to do anything that affects today's voting.
45分钟之前
Forty-five minutes ago,
我们突袭了穆罕默德·卡拉比的住处  先生
we raided the home of Muhammed Kalabi, sir.
在戴德里克大街
On Deaderick Ave.
-嗯  -那里离体育场很近
- Yes. - It's near the Coliseum.
嫌疑人不在公寓里
The suspect was not in his apartment,
但是我们发现了制造炸弹的材料
but we did find bomb-making material.
-天哪  -米切
- Jesus, uh... - Now, Mitch...
我们最不希望的就是让你恐慌
the last thing we want is for you to panic.
你一定要知道联邦政府
You must know that you have the full support
会全力支持你
of the federal government here.
接下来怎么办
Um, it... Well, what... what's next?
我们相信他的目标是某个投票中心
We believe his target is one of the voting centers.
我们知道你已经安排了警卫队
We know you have soldiers in place,
采取了安全措施  设置了检查站
security measures and checkpoints.
格林局长正赶去见你
Director Green is on his way to you.
联调局诺克斯维尔办事处会设立指挥中心
There will be a command center out of the FBI office in Knoxville
我们将进行协调
where we will coordinate.
我的家人今早就在体育场投了票
My family voted at the Coliseum this morning.
米切  听我说
Mitch, listen to me.
不管你需要什么  我们都会提供
Whatever you need, we will provide.
俄亥俄的数字怎么样
How are the Ohio numbers?
投票率这么低  不好估计
It's hard to gauge with turnout this low.
就是要这效果
That was kind of the point.
是对于另一方  不是民主党
For the other side, not Democrats.
州长担心了  你有什么数据吗
The governor's worried. Do you have any numbers?
没有  只有我们给过你的
No, just what we gave you.
我以为总统可能有
I would think that the president might have
我们接触不到的数据
access to some numbers that we don't.
如果我有  你也会有
When I get them, you'll get them.
-我们很担心  -坚持住
- We're worried. - Hang in there.
等过了3点这一波我再跟你联系
I'll touch base with you after the three o'clock wave.
请让我单独待会儿  谢谢
If you could all just give me a moment, please. Thank you.
你最好去宴会厅
You better head over to the ballroom.
我们其中一人应该到场
One of us should make an appearance.
先生  这一天终于到了
Sir, the day has finally arrived.
是啊  让我们看看这一天有多长吧
Yes, and let's see just how long this day lasts.
想像一下国安局给我打电话问
Imagine my surprise when the NSA called me
穆罕默德·卡拉比的事时我有多惊讶吧
about Muhammed Kalabi just...
你的电话随后就到
moments before you did.
情况还在发展
Situation is still unfolding.
在选举日
On Election Day?
弗兰西斯
Francis...
跟你共事真是一段独特的经历
it's been quite a journey working with you.
卡拉比溜进了国内
Kalabi slipped into the country,
他正策划着一起针对
and he's planning a terrorist attack
田纳西某个投票中心的恐怖袭击
against a voting center in Tennessee.
这种说法太吓人了
And that is a terrifying proposition.
我需要你在白宫
Well, I may need you to stay around
再多待一阵  凯茜
the White House a bit longer, Cathy,
直到事态平息
until this situation is resolved.
好的
Of course.
我只是说
I was only saying...
这一路以来很不错了
it's been a good run.
说得像她能激怒我似的
As if she could ever get under my skin.
我现在还不用去宴会
I don't need to get to the party just yet.
人们伸着汗涔涔的手想要最后一次向我致敬
Sweaty palms, eager to pay me their last respects.
但他们真正想用的致敬方式
When what they really want to do to show their respect
是把所有子弹都射向我
is to empty their bullets in my body,
确保我死得透透的
just to make sure that I'm dead.
帕特  抱歉让你久等了
Patti, I'm so sorry to keep you waiting.
哈维女士刚刚告诉我
Miss Harvey was just telling me
日程安排有变
that there's been a change in the schedule.
是啊  很不幸现在出现了紧急情况
Yes, unfortunately, we're in a bit of an emergency.
但我希望能尽快解决
But I hope it will be resolved soon.
汤姆  你好
Tom, hello.
-你认识耶茨先生吧  -认识
- You know Mr. Yates, don't you? - Yes,
党代会上见过
we met at the convention.
莉安会在酒店
So LeAnn will be at the hotel.
要是你觉得
She can reach me
我应该早点而不是晚点过去的话  她会联系我
if you feel I need to be there sooner rather than later.
万一是晚点过去
In case it's later...
我希望你考虑一下四年后
I want you to think four years down the road.
-你说什么  -他们信赖你
- I'm sorry? - They trust you.
四年可转瞬即逝
Four years is no time.
有辆车在等您
We have a car waiting.
我们今天还握手了
So we're shaking hands today?
我们还是保持那样最好
I think it's best we keep it like that.
要握得像真格的一样
Well, shake it like you mean it.
这样如何
How's that?
你希望我直接去宴会厅吗
So you want me to just head over to the ballroom?
不
No.
我确实喜欢穿过大房间看你
I do like looking at you across a large room.
胜利
Victory.
你赢的话用这份
This is for when you win.
败选演说我也写了一份
I wrote a concession speech as well.
还有时间
全国上下的投票点都加强了安保
With increased security at polling places across the country,
康威拿下印第安纳  密西西比  佛罗里达
今年进行投票的美国人
will fewer Americans vote for the president this year
会不会比以往都少
than in any election in recent memory?
尤其受关注的是典型的摇摆州
Particular attention is being paid to typical battleground states,
俄亥俄和宾夕法尼亚
Ohio and Pennsylvania,
在这些州  投票人数成了核心问题
where voter turnout has become a central issue
这可能决定本次历史性大选的结果
that could make all the difference in this historic election.
费城的投票率如果很低
You know, if turnout is low in Philadelphia...
安德伍德夫妇就输定了
the Underwoods are going under.
你得想个更好的开场白
You need a better in than that.
你看起像是被折腾得不轻
You look like you've been chewed up and shit out twice today.
似乎难以集中精力
Seems like you're having trouble focusing.
你看过医生吗
You ever see a doctor about that?
什么
What?
因为我自信可以诊断你是
Oh, 'cause I feel pretty comfortable diagnosing you
心事太重了
with too much on your fucking mind.
我请你喝一杯吧  我在庆祝
Let me get you something real. I'm celebrating.
两杯奥本威士忌
Two Oban.
庆祝什么
Celebrating what?
你知道汤姆·汉默施密特的长期调查组吧
You know Tom Hammerschmidt's long lead team?
你面前的这位是新加入的成员
You're looking at the newest member.
那人真是永不放弃
That guy never gives up.
我告诉你他想干什么  你给他提供消息
I tell you what he's up to, feed him things from you.
现在谈交换条件  有点晚了吧
Don't you think it's a little late for quid pro quo?
安德伍德夫妇仍有胜算
The Underwoods could still win.
等着瞧吧
We'll see.
无论如何  你都还有几个月
Either way, you still have a couple more months.
也对
Yeah.
我会找到地方落脚的
I'll land somewhere.
你的电话
Your phone.
今天有人能让我消停一会儿吗
Can somebody give me a second today, you know?
该死  失陪一下
Shit. Excuse me.
你好
Hello?
有报告称...
...while reports are coming in
诺克斯维尔一投票中心可能发生了袭击
of a possible attack at a Knoxville voting center.
我们来看看直播...
Now, let's take a live look...
诺克斯维尔投票中心发生事故
田纳西州
诺克斯维尔
田纳西州  田纳西怎么了
Tennessee? What's going on in Tennessee?
目前场面非常混乱
...it's a very chaotic scene at the moment.
什么
What?
目前情况很复杂
...there's a lot happening right now.
当然  警方正在
Police are... are, of course,
试图安抚民众  并保证大家的安全
trying to keep everyone calm and safe here.
我们将为您带来
And we will bring you...
你到底去哪了
Where the hell were you?
田纳西  田纳西到底怎么回事
Tennessee. What the hell's going on in Tennessee?
穆罕默德·卡拉比
Muhammed Kalabi,
叙利亚哈里发国的  烧肖像的那个
the ICO guy from Syria who burned the effigy.
有什么计划
What's the plan?
今晚我站在你们面前  作为副总统候选人
I stand before you this evening as vice presidential candidate,
作为美国的第一夫人
as the First Lady of the United States,
最重要的  也作为这个伟大国家的一名公民
and most of all... as a citizen of this great country.
虽然诺克斯维尔投票中心发生了暴力事件
Despite the violent incident at the voting center in Knoxville,
此时此刻  总统正在进行处理
which the president is attending to as we speak,
我们想向任何在考虑不投票的各位保证
we want to assure anyone who's considering not voting
现在投票不仅是安全的  更是你们的责任
that it is not only safe to vote, it is your duty to do so.
不管你是民主党人
It doesn't matter if you're a Democrat.
还是共和党人
It doesn't matter if you're a Republican.
我们的国家需要你们今天去投票
Our nation needs you to vote today.
暴力不能导致冷漠
Violence cannot beget apathy.
我们必须发声
We must make our voices heard.
赛斯
Seth!
有目击者称  诺克斯维尔投票中心
Witnesses report an FBI and Homeland presence
出现了联调局和国安局的人
at the Knoxville voting center.
你觉得这事跟哈利发国有关吗
Do you believe this is ICO-related?
赛斯  拜托
Seth, please! Come on.
-联调局没有回应  -你也别乱说  吉娜
- And the FBI isn't talking. - Neither are you, Gina.
这可不是发布会  我并没做相关安排
This isn't a presser, because I didn't schedule one.
-我们只想知道  -两次了  吉娜
- We're just trying to find out-- - That's two, Gina.
如果你想三振出局  我很乐意效劳
If you're looking for a strikeout, I'm happy to oblige.
不想吗  很好
No? Good.
目前不接受提问
There's no questions at this time.
第一夫人的声明里该说的都说了
The First Lady's statement stands as is.
我得到田纳西的最新情况就会通报
I will have updates for you on Tennessee as I get them.
所有人都清楚了吗  谢谢
Is everyone clear? Thank you.
赛斯
Seth!
我听说一切都乱套了
I'm told everything just went wrong.
-联调局派了拆弹部队的人  -但是  米切
- The FBI had the bomb guys there... - But, Mitch...
天啊
...for crying out loud!
伤情仅仅是擦伤和瘀伤
...injuries didn't go beyond scrapes and bruises.
这我可不确定  肖娜
Oh, I don't know about that, Shawna.
有12人被送往了医院
Twelve people were taken to the hospital.
格林的预计到达时间有了吗
Look, is there any status on Green's ETA?
-斯图尔特州务卿和我  -好的  请稍等
- Secretary Stewart and I... - Yes. Just a moment, sir.
-无法做出决断  除非  -您得接这通电话
- ...cannot make a determination without-- - You need to take this.
什么  什么
What? What?
又怎么了
What the hell is this?
你好
Hello.
州长  我是马克·厄舍
Governor. Mark Usher here.
我们应该在太阳谷的会议上见过
I think we met at the conference in Sun Valley.
对  没错
Yes, that's right.
真希望能在更好的情况下打来
Well, I wish I were calling under better circumstances.
我想知道您有什么需求
I wanted to know what you're going to need.
我可以尽快安排人过去  以防您...
I can get some excellent people down there fast in case you...
您似乎需要额外的安保  或者
you're feeling like you need the extra security or...
您还在听吗
You there?
在  我在
I'm right here, yeah.
几分钟前我跟肖娜谈过了
I spoke to Shawna a few minutes ago,
我们一致认为绝不能让选举受影响
and we agreed that we absolutely cannot disrupt this election.
你联系了我的州务卿
You called my secretary of state?
是她联系了我
Well, she called me.
她是田纳西州党领袖  跟你一样
She is a leader of the party in Tennessee. As are you.
需要我提醒你  先生  你那儿是共和党州
Do I need to remind you, sir, that yours is a red state,
共和党人都指望着你呢吗
and every Republican in it is counting on you?
-谢谢  厄舍先生  -等一下
- Thank you, Mr. Usher. - Now, hold on.
肖娜只想问
Shawna just wanted to ask
能做什么  做不了什么
what can be done and what can't be done.
她跟我们其他人一样  也在想办法
She's like the rest of us, trying to figure this thing out.
因为目前尚无法确定的
Because of the scale of a possible threat
诺克斯维尔投票中心疏散
田纳西州诺克斯维尔
潜在威胁的规模
which we're still trying to determine,
也因为这些投票中心的重要性
and because of the importance of these, uh, voting centers,
我们请求州长宣布
we're asking the governor to declare
-进入紧急状态  -威尔  你坐会儿吧
- a state of emergency... - Will, could you please sit?
这样我们才能...
...so that we can provide more...
我不喜欢这样
I don't like it.
3点那波说田纳西无论如何都是我们的了
Three o'clock wave said Tennessee's locked up, no matter what.
...发生在这里的事件
...into the event that took place here...
亲爱的  大家都看不到了
Love, no one can see.
怎么回事
What the hell?
可能会让人不安
...be potentially disturbing.
有炸弹时狗不会叫的
They don't bark when there's a bomb.
什么意思"不会叫"
What do you mean, "They don't bark"?
有炸弹时狗不会叫  总统先生
The canine units don't bark when there's a bomb, Mr. President.
嗯  但整栋楼的人都听到了
Yeah, but the whole building heard it.
他们的训练是检测到炸弹就坐下
They're trained to sit down when they detect a bomb.
-它们坐下了吗  -没有
- So did they sit down? - No.
那就是没炸弹
Then there was no bomb.
我们认为狗叫是因为受到了刺激
We think the barking was provoked.
刺激  格林局长  这真是够了
Provoked? Director Green, that'll be enough.
这些狗是我们最后的防线  先生
These dogs are our last line of defense, sir.
我觉得哈里发国今天闯进去了
I think ICO got in there today.
幸好他们没引爆炸弹
And thank God they didn't get a bomb off,
但不管他们让什么人混了进去
but whatever operative they got in there,
我觉得是去引发暴乱的
I think, was used to provoke the riot.
我说够了
I said that is enough.
你觉得哈里发国会闯进楼里
You think ICO got all the way in that building
然后又决定还是不引爆炸弹了吗
and then just decided not to set off a bomb?
-这个...  -我们不能影响投票
- Well, there are-- - We are not going to disrupt the voting.
米切  你好好劝劝他
Mitch, would you please talk some sense into him?
-我  -如果不暂停投票
- I-- - If we don't suspend,
局里无法确保中心的安全
the Bureau cannot guarantee the safety of these centers.
不可接受  找到卡拉比
Unacceptable. Find Kalabi.
州长不会希望
The governor does not wanna
在这么晚的时候颁发宵禁令
have to institute a curfew this late in the game.
-米切  -是  先生
- And, Mitch... - Uh, yes, sir.
你不能关闭投票
...you are not closing the polls.
你觉得我们该关吗
You think we should?
我没法发表意见
I can't weigh in on this.
我得跟肖娜谈谈
I need to talk to Shawna.
公众还要承受多少丑闻
How many scandals should the public be expected to endure
汤姆·汉默施密特
《华盛顿先驱报》
才会说"够了"
before they say, "Enough"?
会说"我不出门了"
Before they say, "I'm staying home"?
会对国家完全丧失信心
Before they lose complete faith in this democratic republic?
上次出现这样的趋势
This is a trend that dates back at least
是尼克松躲过牢狱之灾的时候
to when Nixon avoided jail time.
好了  结束
Okay, we're out.
-真不错  -我不需要粉丝  肖恩
- You're good. - I don't need fans, Sean.
只是真诚的欣赏
Just genuine appreciation.
喝一杯吗  一杯是酒  一杯不是
Would you like a drink? One is brown and one is not.
-今晚会很漫长  -我听说不是
- It's gonna be a long night. - That's not what I hear.
那么  田纳西
So, Tennessee...
是问题所在
Is the question.
怎么样
And?
我的男伴什么都不知道
My date knew nothing.
你在到处问了吗
Are you making the rounds?
这里的人比我一般接触的年龄要大
Crowd's a little older than I'm used to, but...
但是  没错  他们话多  却没什么料
yes, they're a talkative bunch... that don't say much.
我要酒
I'll take the brown one.
那是帕特里夏·惠特克  民主党全国委员会主席
That's Patricia Whittaker over there. Chairperson of the DNC.
她有次在奥马哈一家酒吧里扇了我个耳光
She slapped me once in a bar in Omaha.
我也不知道为什么
For the life of me, I can't tell you why.
田纳西州有问题
There's something wrong with Tennessee.
你的男伴要么在撒谎  要么在抵赖
Your date is either lying or denying.
这是什么意思
What did you mean by this?
演讲背后的字
On the back of the speech?
没事  别提了
Nothing. Forget it.
"还有时间"
"There's still time"?
还有时间做什么
There's still time for what?
你在干什么
What are you doing?
你和你丈夫
You and your husband.
准备赢得选举
Getting ready to win an election.
我看到你的样子了
I see the way you're acting.
你知道我们今天打算赢得选举吗
Do you realize we have every intention of winning today?
当然
Sure.
但然后呢
But then what?
我以前会去缅因州的一间小木屋
I used to go to this cabin... up in Maine.
窗户关不严实
The windows don't close properly.
整个夏天都能闻到大海的气味儿
You can smell the ocean all summer long.
我觉得你还是去宴会厅吧
I do think it's better you go to the ballroom.
如果你尚未投票  我保证  你会有机会的
If you have not voted, I assure you, you will get the chance.
但出于良心
But I cannot, in good conscience,
我不能在确保安全前  允许投票继续
allow balloting to continue until I am satisfied that it is safe.
为此  随着夜晚将至
To that end, as nightfall approaches,
我要宣布今晚
I am announcing an enforced,
执行全州宵禁
state-wide curfew, effective tonight.
如果你中部时间晚8点30还未回家
If you are not in your home by 8:30 p.m. central time,
或是东部时间9点30
or by 9:30 in the eastern parts of this state,
你将被拘禁甚至逮捕
you will be subject to detention and possible arrest.
这是怎么回事
What the hell's going on?
我们会赢下宾州和俄亥俄州  就这么回事
What's going on is we're gonna win Pennsylvania and Ohio.
那么你就超过270了
That puts you over 270.
投票还在继续  大家还在投票
The polls are still open. People are still voting.
我的直觉是那些票属于我们
My gut says they're ours.
没有田纳西也272了
That's 272 without Tennessee.
那混蛋暂停了投票
That asshole's suspending the vote.
那得由他的州务卿决定  她是我们的人
That's up to his secretary of state, and she's on our side.
-都这样了她还有的选吗  -州长  听我说
- She's gonna have a choice after this? - Governor, listen to me.
我们还要让弗兰西斯·安德伍德
I mean, how long do we let Francis Underwood
耍这种手段多久啊
get away with this kind of shit? Huh? How long?
他不会得逞的
He won't get away with it.
不会的
He won't.
刚刚是田纳西州长
That was Tennessee governor...
相信我
Trust me.
宣布全州宵禁
...announcing a state-wide curfew.
扯淡
Bullshit.
全州的投票中心都在关闭
Voting centers all across the state are being shut down,
中部时间8点30或东部时间9点30前
and anyone not in their homes 8:30 central time,
还没回家的人
or 9:30...
费城5点的一波  我们应该赢定了
Five o'clock wave from Philly. I think we're home.
...被拘禁甚至逮捕  这则公告...
...detention and possible arrest. This announcement...
田纳西的事简直疯了
That Tennessee shit is crazy.
疯狂事经常有
Crazy shit happens all the time.
这么凑巧
This convenient?
少来什么阴谋论了
Spare me the conspiracy talk.
政府没那么大威力  或能力
The government's not that powerful... or competent.
总得问问
A man can ask.
目前安德伍德255  康威245
We're looking at 255 Underwood, 245 Conway.
宾州和俄亥俄呢
Pennsylvania and Ohio?
还是太接近  但就要6点了
Still too close, but it's almost six o' clock.
等我们把田纳西州从康威变成摇摆
When we change Tennessee from Conway to undecided--
那么康威会下跌
That brings Conway down
-到...  -234  还是太接近
- to-- - Two thirty-four. Still way too close.
是啊  我们尚不知道
Yes, but we don't yet know
他已经拿下了西部州
that he's locked in the western states.
那些州十年没变了
Those states have been locked up for ten years.
红的  红的  红的  到今晚结束又会是红的
Red, red, red and they'll be red again by the end of the night.
就看宾州和俄亥俄了
It's gonna come down to Pennsylvania and Ohio.
康威需要两个州  你只需要一个
Conway needs both. You only need one.
马修斯
Matthews?
他会反抗  可能还会公开表态
He'll push back. He might even go public.
另外五个州呢
What about the other five states in play?
律师在候着
The lawyers are waiting.
我们可以就压制投票提出诉讼  但是
We can generate lawsuits, argue suppression, but...
还是不够
Still not enough.
奥姆斯泰德在俄亥俄情况不乐观  他很不高兴
Olmstead's losing in Ohio, and he's not taking it well.
我今早跟他的幕僚长塔妮娅通过话
I spoke with his chief of staff, Tanya, this morning.
他在州北的情况很糟
He's getting clobbered in the northern part of the state.
克利夫兰的低投票率也是个问题
Low turnout in Cleveland's not helping.
但他还能扭转局势
But he could still pull it out.
他赢不了的  他也清楚
He's not going to win and he knows it.
我们还有多少时间
How much time do we have?
俄亥俄州两小时后关闭  大部分人今早都投票了
Ohio closes in two hours. And most people voted this morning.
有些州局势已定了
Some of these states are baked in already.
克莱尔和我要单独谈谈
Claire and I need the room for a moment.
是  先生
Yes, sir.
-莉安  我们再联络你  -是  先生
- LeAnn, we'll call you back. - Yes, sir.
你为什么让他出去
Why did you ask him to leave?
因为我想再看着你的眼睛一次
Because I just wanted to look in your eyes one more time
再决定要不要动手
before we do this.
弗兰西斯
Francis...
我们做吧
we're doing this.
他救不了我们  他发明了任期限制
He can't save us. He invented term limits.
道格
Doug!
再给我接莉安·哈维
Get me LeAnn Harvey back on the phone.
是  先生
Yes, sir.
对俄亥俄做该做的吧
Do what you have to do with Ohio.
我就去
I'm on it.
莉安  让律师准备
LeAnn, get the lawyers ready.
-我不能这么做  -你可以的
- I can't do this. - Yes, you can.
-不不  -而且得马上完成
- No, no, no, no, no! - And it needs to be done quickly.
太草率了
It's too sloppy.
是莉安打的电话  为什么是你来
Why are you here if LeAnn called me?
我还要向你解释
Do I really have to explain to you
你不这么做的后果吗
what will happen if you don't do this?
我不在乎他输不输
I don't care if he loses.
我不是指选举  我是说你
I'm not talking about the election. I'm talking about you.
你会怎么样
What will happen to you?
你有你需要的一切了  链接已经发给你了
You have everything you need. The Pastebin link was sent to you.
莉安呢
Where's LeAnn?
她不在  我时间不多了
She's not here, and I'm short on time.
州长  对不起  但这事只有一个办法
Governor, I'm sorry, but there's only one way to play this.
我们需要你撤掉那三郡的
We need you to pull your poll workers
投票工作人员和投票机
and your machines from those three counties.
共和党人会宰了我的  那是他们的地盘
The Republicans would crucify me. They own that area.
但那几个选区
But those are the precincts
最有可能遭遇威胁
that are most likely to be threatened.
"可能"  你什么...
"Likely to be"? Hey, what are you...
这是什么意思
What are we talking about here?
恐怖袭击可能性
Terrorist chatter.
针对田纳西州的
Related to Tennessee?
是的
Yes, sir.
我可不能光听你空口一词
Well, I'm gonna need more than your word on that.
对不起  但情报是机密  州长
Oh, I'm sorry, but the intelligence is classified, Governor.
那给我权限
Then read me in.
我没亲眼
'Cause I'm not doing this
看到证据是不会这么做的
without seeing tangible proof with my own eyes.
你去告诉弗兰西斯吧
You can tell Francis.
另外  因为俄亥俄州投票率这么低
The other thing is, with Ohio turnout so low,
可能会有人指控你刻意压制投票
people could accuse you of engaging in voter suppression.
什么
What?
投票中心和警卫队都是总统的主意
The voting centers and the troops were the president's idea.
但你同意了
But you signed on to them,
这才重要
and that's what matters.
你要输掉选举了  先生
You're losing your election, sir.
这很明显
The signs are clear.
民主党失去一位州长就太可惜了
That'd be a real shame for the Democrats to be down a governor.
但现在发生了种种情况
But here we have this confluence of events.
一方面是你不尽如人意的选情
Your disappointing returns on one hand
一方面是恐怖袭击的可能
and the chatter on the other.
我需要证据  否则  人们会觉得
I need proof. Otherwise, people will think--
你为了赢得选举  而关闭了
That you shut down voting in Republican precincts
共和党选区的投票站
to guarantee your own win.
幸好
Now I'd say it's a good thing
国安局刚收到了可靠的消息
that the NSA just picked up on some credible chatter.
这危险的世界让你别无选择
This dangerous world left you no choice.
谢谢
Thank you.
州长  我刚刚拿到了机密情报
Governor, I was just handed the classified intel.
您在加密服务器上吗
Are you on a secure server?
-在  -请稍等
- Yes, I am. - Please hold.
我这就把文件发给您
I'm sending the files over right now.
取消           发送
您的决定是正确的  先生
You're doing the right thing, sir.
我们可不能背上血债
We don't want blood on our hands.
我不管他们把投票机搬哪去
I don't care where they're taking the voting machines.
你就盯紧...
Just stay...
有必要的话把你自己绑在投票机上
You chain yourself to one of them if you have to.
好  我去找个俄亥俄州的法官
Good. I'm gonna find an Ohio judge.
俄亥俄州的投票中心已经关了近两个小时了
Voting centers in Ohio have been closed for almost two hours.
康威已经去找法官了
And Conway's got a judge.
他在申请重开投票中心
He's petitioning to reopen.
但就算投票中心继续关闭
But even if they stay closed,
俄亥俄州能帮我们达成目的吗
would Ohio get us there?
其他州可能还有戏
Other states might be in play.
压制投票的传言也出现了  但...
Rumblings of suppression are out there, although...
还有什么别的情况
Well, what else do we have?
爱达荷州  出现恐吓选民的事件
Voter intimidation in Idaho.
怎么样  我要不要回话让他们提交诉讼
What do you think? Should I call them back and have them file?
我看行
I like it.
这样和田纳西的事呼应效果最好
It has the most resonance with what's happened in Tennessee.
我还希望佐治亚有议员站出来
I also like an assemblyman we have in Georgia.
马里兰有个众议员
There's a congressman in Maryland.
马里兰也是没要求派警卫队的州之一
That's one of the states that didn't request the troops.
等等  我们需不需要普通选民出来表态
But wait. Don't we need something coming from a voter?
密西西比有个选民
There's a voter in Mississippi.
她说她吓得不敢去投票了
Said she was too scared to vote.
新闻基本就是告诉她不要去投票
That TV essentially told her not to go.
这就有点牵强了吧
Well, that sounds like a bit of a stretch.
可能对我们有利  先生
That could be a plus for us, sir.
能很好地打开局面
Really open things up.
如果俄亥俄继续关闭
If Ohio stays shut,
可能会引发连锁反应
there could be a ripple effect.
这都是前无古人的做法
This is all uncharted territory.
那好  佐治亚和马里兰待会儿再说
All right, let's put a pin in Georgia and Maryland,
让俄亥俄的投票中心继续关闭
and let's keep the Ohio voting centers shut down,
看看有什么结果
and see where that gets us.
康威已经拿下宾夕法尼亚
Pennsylvania has gone to Conway.
康威拿下宾夕法尼亚
就算双方在俄亥俄仍然难分胜负
Even if Ohio is still too close to call
总统在西北部取胜的话
and the President does well in the Northwest,
他仍无法抵消康威在南部取得的优势
he can't counter Conway's gains in the South,
而那里曾是安德伍德的地盘
in what would typically be Underwood territory.
人民已经做出了选择
The people have spoken.
真是难以置信
I can't believe this.
总统因故不能前来  他向各位表示歉意
The President apologizes that he couldn't be here tonight,
但他想让我告诉各位  败选已经不可避免了
but he wanted me to let you know that concession is inevitable.
还有那么多州票没计完
All the states haven't been called yet.
总统还有时间想办法...
The president still has time if he needs...
各位  我们已经尽力了
Guys, we fought a good fight.
可是很不幸  实情就是这样
But, unfortunately, this is the reality of the situation.
天啊
Jesus.
看来这就算完了
Well, I guess that's that.
喂  我是威尔
Yeah, this is Will.
我想第一个对你说
I wanted to be the first to tell you
恭喜你  当选总统先生
congratulations, Mr. President-elect.
谢谢你  总统先生
Well, thank you, Mr. President.
2000年大选夜  戈尔先向小布什认输
但是第二天又反悔了
怎么  你以为我没从戈尔那里学到教训吗
What? You think I learned nothing from Al Gore?
我们这场选战可真是激烈万分啊  是不是
We kept them on the edge of their seats, didn't we?
我想这也说明我们的体制运转良好
I guess that means the system is working.
我也这么看
I guess it does.
你是我遇到过的最强劲的对手了  弗兰西斯
You're about as tough an opponent as they come, Francis.
我经验丰富啊
Well, I've had a lot of practice.
请一定要转达我对汉娜和孩子们的问候
Now, you be sure to give my regards to Hannah and the children.
谢谢你  总统先生  我
Thank you, Mr. President. I'm...
我在不久的将来  肯定会向你讨教的
sure I'll be calling on you for advice in the very near future.
我万分期待
Well, I look forward to that.
他认输了
He conceded?
对
Yeah.
我们成功了
We did it.
我们做到了
打扰一下  先生
Excuse me, sir.
布洛哈特将军正在来套房的路上
General Brockhart is on his way over to the suite.
谢谢
Thank you.
安德伍德总统是否已认输
有消息源称  不久前
Sources are telling us that Francis Underwood
弗兰西斯·安德伍德致电康威州长
conceded to Governor Conway on the phone
承认落选
only a short time ago.
我猜测他们收到的数字跟我们的相符
I suspect their numbers are matching up with ours,
安德伍德总统是否已认输
那么俄亥俄将被共和党收入囊中
which would put Ohio in the Republican column.
足以让威廉·康威
Enough to make William Conway
成为美国下一任总统
the next president of the United States.
-你好  -塔妮娅  让他接电话
- Hello? - Tanya, put him on the line.
等一下  我看看能不能找到他
Hang on, let me see if I can get him.
他是我的州务卿
He's my Secretary of State,
他有权这么做
and he has the power to do it.
那你得告诉他该做什么
Well, then you need to tell him what to do.
他说他可以重开选站将投票日延长到明天
He says he can reopen and extend the voting day into tomorrow.
告诉他这不安全
Tell him it's not safe.
我说了  道格
I've done that, Doug!
他显然不在乎
Obviously, he doesn't seem to care.
安德伍德已经认输了
Underwood conceded already.
别放你的州务卿出去
Do not trot out your Secretary of State.
投票不能重启
Voting cannot resume.
如果你还有什么疑虑
Now, if you have any doubt,
那也给我忍着
you swallow it right now.
我担心的是党派
I'm worried about the party.
这对党派的影响
What this could do to the party.
罗杰  这比党派重要多了
Roger, this is so much bigger than the party.
我觉得我把我的事业都赌上了
I feel like I'm risking my entire career here.
是的
You are.
如果你不照我说的做
And if you don't do what I'm telling you,
你的前途就完了
it's over for sure.
怎么了
What?
他还要耗多久
How many hours is it gonna take him
才肯在公众面前说出那几个字
to spit out the fucking words in public?
不管了  去他的规程
Screw this. Screw protocol.
我这就要过去
I'm heading down there.
-不  不行  -已经到第二天了  马克
- No, you're not. - It's already tomorrow, Mark.
这简直不可理喻
I mean, this is insane.
-我想发表讲话  -俄亥俄州还没完
- I want to make my speech! - Ohio is still in play.
什么
What?
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
持续的恐怖主义威胁带来的恐慌...
...fear from continued terrorist threats
和田纳西州传出的令人不安的消息
and the disturbing news coming out of Tennessee...
让我不得不关闭几个我们的投票站
I was forced to close a number of our polling places.
操
Fuck me.
经与俄亥俄州州务卿达成一致
And in accordance with the Ohio secretary of state,
投票在进一步通知前先行暂停
the vote is suspended until further notice.
我知道这会让我们的选民疑虑重重
Now, I know this may put our electorates in question...
但我别无选择
...but I had no choice.
新泽西可能不认证
New Jersey might not certify.
出现了一些异常情况
There's been a variety of irregularities.
伊利诺伊也是
Same with Illinois.
看起来内华达也有异动
Looks like Nevada's making noises, too.
感觉似曾相识  你有同感吗
I'm having déjà vu. You ever get that?
你真的在问我似曾相识的感觉吗
Are you seriously asking me about déjà vu?
算了  已经没感觉了
Never mind. It's gone.
你从未有过似曾相识的感觉吗  人人都会有
You never get déjà vu? Everybody does.
我没有
I don't.
别那么焦虑  道格
Don't look so worried, Doug.
你就是那一瞬间感觉很熟悉
You just felt familiar for a second.
已经过去了
It's over.
现在  总统选举结果未定
Now, the presidency hangs in the balance.
部分州不能认证结果
至少六个州将不能在2016的选举夜
At least six states will not have certified vote totals
部分州不能认证结果
认证计票结果
on Election Night 2016.
晚上好
Good evening.
我猜我该说早上好
I guess I should say good morning.
威尔很希望他能亲自出镜
Will wishes he could be here himself...
但我们获知那有违规章
but we've been advised that goes against protocol.
我知道...
I know...
你们很失望
you're disappointed.
你介意用失望这个词吗
Are you okay with the word disappointed?
我们不该提到他们的愤怒吗
Shouldn't we acknowledge their outrage?
我觉得我们应该小心处理
I'd say we should tread lightly.
目前我们只想请他们保持耐心
For now, we're just asking for their patience.
好  我们拍吧
Okay, let's do it.
汉娜·康威就结果发表讲话
这个国家就没有无聊的时候
Never a dull moment in this country.
汉娜·康威就结果发表讲话
威尔很希望他能亲自出镜
Will wishes he could be here himself,
但我们获知那有违规章
but we've been advised that would go against protocol.
我知道你们很失望
I know you're disappointed
你们所期待的改变
that the change you were hoping for...
你们所投票支持的改变
...that you voted for,
得再等一段时间
has to wait a little longer.
艾·麦卡伦莉  我受不了了  对不起  麦卡...
最终  这没有定论的选举之夜
And, finally, a night of electoral indecision,
大选之夜的混乱
几乎每个州都提起了诉讼
with lawsuits being filed in nearly every state,
为它画上句号的是檀香山市长
has ended with the mayor of Honolulu,
最后一个关闭了投票
in the last state to close its polls,
并拒绝承认选举结果
refusing to honor the results of the election
还提起了诉讼
and filing a lawsuit.
夏威夷是我们这边的吗
Was Hawaii one of ours?
应该不是
No, I don't think so.
克莱尔  能帮我个忙吗
Claire, could you do me a little favor?
我头很痛
I have a splitting headache.
你能揉揉我的太阳穴吗
Could you rub my temples for a moment?
当然
Of course.
不  其实是我眼睛这里疼
No, actually the pain is right behind my eyes.
你能...给我揉揉眼睛吗
Could you just... rub my eyes for me?
但是你讨厌那样
But you hate that.
我知道  但是这次我应该会喜欢
I know, but I think I'll like it this time.
你可以用力点
You can do it harder.
再用力点
Even harder than that.
走出这一步就没有回头路了
There's no coming back from this.
我很清楚我们要做什么
I know exactly what we're about to do.
如果我们失败了  后果要我们两个承担
If we fail, it's on both of us.
我是不能保护你的
I won't be able to protect you.
那就如释重负了
And what a relief that will be...
对我们两个都是
for both of us.
美国人民不知道什么对他们才是最好的
The American people don't know what's best for them.
我知道
I do.
我很清楚他们需要什么
I know exactly what they need.
他们就像小孩子  克莱尔
They're like little children, Claire.
我们从未有过的孩子
Children we never had.
我们得抓着他们黏糊糊的手指
We have to hold their sticky fingers
擦干净他们的脏嘴
and wipe their filthy mouths.
教他们分辨是非
Teach them right from wrong.
告诉他们思考什么
Tell them what to think
感觉什么  想要什么
and how to feel and what to want.
他们甚至连书写最疯狂的梦想
They even need help writing their wildest dreams,
塑造最大的恐惧都需要帮助
crafting their worst fears.
他们很幸运
Lucky for them...
他们有我...
they have me...
他们有你
they have you.
安德伍德
Underwood.
2016年
2016.
2020年
2020.
2024年
2024.
2028年
2028.
2032年
2032.
2036年
2036.
一个国家
One nation...
由安德伍德执掌
Underwood.
道格  莉安  你们有空吗
Doug, LeAnn... do you have a moment?
按约定俗成的规则  正常的选举程序  是在选举结果揭晓后
落败方向胜选方打电话认输  然后发表落选演说  再由胜选方宣布胜利
竞选双方在这件事上  按说要本着"大局为重"的原则
就是不能让胜负的结果影响选民对民主制度的信任
所以如果选举中出现选票极其接近的情况  而落后方要求重新计票
落后方会面临压力  不能让这个悬而未决的时间拖得太久  造成混乱
但如果有候选人想纠缠下去  拖上几个月  也并不被法律禁止
在2016年大选夜  希拉里开始并不甘心认输
是奥巴马亲自给她打电话  要求她认输  她才给特朗普打电话承认落选
但她并没去自己的选举中心会场公开认输  并感谢支持者
而是在午夜后派自己的竞选经理去会场  告知支持者事情还没完
媒体是在她不会亲临现场后  才得知她致电特朗普认输了  当时场面混乱
美国建国时并没有任期限制  但是首任总统华盛顿高风亮节
担任两届总统后就坚决退休  所以后来者也就约定俗成地只任两届
格罗弗·克利夫兰是美国唯一一个卸任后重选再度当选的总统
他是第22任和第24任总统  都只任了一届
但到了富兰克林·罗斯福的时候  因为他影响很大  又遇上二战
所以当他两届任期结束后决定继续做总统时  并没有遇到太多阻力
他的支持者称  他继续担任总统是为了战争需要
罗斯福四次胜选  但是最后一次被选上后不久就因病去世
他的行为被认为是对民主制度的威胁
于是国会在1944年通过了宪法第22条修正案  规定总统最多只能任两届
在副总统中途继位的情况下  也最多只能担任10年